[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle：如果我们有可以是任意长度的东西，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: If we have something that could be an arbitrary length,
作为JavaScript程序员，我们的GOO工具通常是一个列表，一个数组。
our go to tool as a JavaScript programmer is often a list, an array.
如果我要填充我关心处理的URL列表
If I were to populate a list of the URLs that I cared about handling
到一个数组中，然后我就可以立即访问
into a an array, I then immediately have access to
那些函数式编程技术如映射和归约到变换，
those functional programming techniques like map and reduce to transform,
在这张单子上写，排除这样的事情。
compose, exclude things like this on this list.
让我们尝试将这个URL列表更改为其他内容。
Let's try to change this list of URLs to something else.
也许我们应该让他们成为承诺的清单。
Maybe we should get them into being a list of promises.
我们如何转变？
How do we transform?
我们调用.map。
We call .map.
map是将列表一对一转换的实用程序。
Map is the utility that will transform a list one to one.
我们需要一个谓词函数，
And we're going to need a predicate function,
它吸收了一些值，并给出了一个新的值。
which takes in some value and gives us a new value back out.
有人想过这样的函数吗？
Anybody think of a function like that?
获取文件功能怎么样？
How about the get file function?
查看如何在和中获取单个值
See how it takes a single value in and
返回为已转换的单个值OUT？
returns as a single value out that's been transformed?
在这种情况下，围绕价值的承诺。
In this case a promise wrapped around the value.
太好了，我们还知道它将立即进行Ajax调用。
Great, and we also know that it's going to go ahead make that AJAX call right away.
不仅转化，而且
Not only does the transformation, but
它还负责为我们并行提出所有这三个请求。
it also takes care of making all three of those requests in parallel for us.
我们只需将getFile作为要映射的谓词传递即可。
We simply pass the getFile as our predicate to map.
好极了。我们已经完成了第一步
Excellent. We've done the first step,
这就是所谓的所有这些东西。
which is to call all these things.
现在我们有了一份承诺清单。
And now we have a list of promises.
它们都没有任何输出，与它们一起排序，
None of them have any outputs, sequenced in with them,
而且它们没有被排序在一起。
and they're not sequenced together.
我们说过承诺链只是一种实现一个承诺的方式
Well we talked about a promise chain is just a way to take one promise and
从先前承诺的已解析处理程序返回它。
return it from the resolved handler of a previous promise.
这是一种写承诺的方法，就是把它们连在一起。
That's a method of composing promises, is to chain them together.
很好的构图是由我们的好朋友处理的还原功能。
Well composition is handled by our good friend the reduce function.
如果我调用Reduce，Reduce需要两个参数，两个参数。
If I call reduce, reduce takes two parameters, two arguments.
第一个是谓词函数，所以
The first one is the predicate function, so
我们这里会有一个函数叫做，
we're gonna have a function here called,
我们就叫它合并吧，或者我们可以叫它听起来更好的链。
let's just call it combine or maybe we'll call it chain that sounds better.
我们称它为链实际上不，我要叫它联合。
We'll call it chain actually no, I'm gonna call it combine.
在这里我变得超级优柔寡断
Here I am being super indecisive and
我会告诉你为什么我决定不叫它链条。
I'll tell you why I decided not to call it chain.
然后我们需要一个初始值，这是第二个参数
And then we are going to need an initial value that's the second argument that gets
通过或减少。
passed or reduce.
承诺链的初始值是多少？
What's a good initial value for a promise chain?
一个已经解决的承诺怎么样。
How about an already resolved promise.
你可以手动做到这一点，通过在这里做出承诺，
You could manually do that, by making a Promise here,
它接收解析，并且实际上立即调用解析。
that receives a resolve, and actually calls the resolve right away.
这是一个立竿见影的承诺。
That's an immediately resolved Promise.
不会等待任何事情。
Doesn't wait on anything.
原来有一种速记方法
Turns out there's a shorthand way for
你们中的一些人可能在文档中查找过或看到过。
that, some of you might have looked that up or seen that in documentation.
本机Promise API中内置了名为Promise.Resolve的速记。
There's a shorthand built into the native Promise API called Promise.resolve.
Promise.Resolve创建已解决的承诺，并
Promise.resolve creates a resolved Promise and
如果您将任何内容传递给它，它将使用该值解析承诺。
if you pass anything into it it resolves the Promise with that value.
我们不关心这里的任何价值，我们只关心这样一个事实，
We don't care about any value here, we just care about the fact that,
这是一个很好的初始值开始链接，所以
that's a good initial value to start chaining off of, so
这是我们作为决心承诺的初始价值。
that's our initial value as a resolved Promise.
现在，Combine需要两个参数和
Now, combine needs to take two arguments and
我们所谓的那些当然，我认为更好的是改变这些的名称
what we call those of course, I think it's better to change the names of these
参数，以适合您正在执行的操作的上下文，以便您的代码使
parameters to fit the context of what you're doing so that your code makes
更有意义，而不是总是使用累加器和电流之类的东西。
more sense rather than always using accumulator and current or something.
累加器在这里最合适的名称是什么？
What would the accumulator be called most appropriately here?
我会称之为链条。
I would call it chain.
这就是为什么我没有调用函数链，因为我意识到，
That's why I didn't call the function chain cuz I realized,
我要打电话给我的蓄电器链。
I'm gonna call my accumulator chain.
第一次调用这个谓词时，
The very first time this predicate is called,
链只会是已经解决的初始值承诺。
the chain is just gonna be that already resolved initial value Promise.
但它将继续被更多地和
But it's going to continue to be composed more and
更多的链条，随着我们的前进。
more of that chain as we go along.
我要调用我的累加器链，我要调用我的当前值。
I'm going to call my accumulator chain and I'm going to call my current value.
公关，因为这是我正在处理的承诺。
PR for it's the Promise that I'm dealing with.
有我的两个在一起，我的链子和我的公关，现在我该怎么写它们呢？
There's my two together, my chain and my PR, now how am I going to compose them?
如果我们回想一下我们在练习三中所做的，你写第一个的方式
If we think back to what we did in exercise three, the way you compose one
对另一个人的承诺是归还第一个人的第二个。
Promise to another was to return the second one from the first.
我的链子需要一个。然后
My chain needs to have a .then
&gt；&gt；Kyle：返回Pr。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: That returns the pr.
新的行动产生了一个新的连锁承诺。
And that new operation has produced a new chained Promise.
我需要从我的谓词中返回它。
I need to return that from my predicate.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：现在代码将链接所有
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Now that code will chain all for
无论许诺有多少，都在一起。
of the Promises together regardless of how many Promises there are.
它将创造出一大串古老的承诺。
It will create a big old chain of Promises.
这是链条的样子。
Here's what that chain would look like.
它看起来像p1.then函数
It would look like p1.then function
返回p2。然后函数，
return p2 .then function,
返回p3，依此类推。
return p3 and so on.
我们是去那里的路的一部分。
We're part of the way there.
但我们错过了什么？
But what are we missing?
我们没有将输出排序到链中。
We're not sequencing in the outputs into the chain.
这些输出将去哪里？
Where are those outputs going to go?
他们就在这里。
They're going to go right here.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：现在我们将有一个，如果我把这个写出来。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Now we're going to have a, if I were to write this out.
我们有一个Promise.Resolve，是我们的初始值，
We have a Promise.resolve, is our initial value,
.然后函数返回p1。
.then function return p1.
你注意到我有立即的，然后输出。
And you notice I have the immediate .then output on it.
&GT；&GT；Kyle：每个人都看到我是如何展开的，我们在Reduce中做了什么？
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Everybody see how I'm unrolling that, what we're doing in the reduce?
这就是我们的Reduce中正在发生的事情的可视展开，所以
That's the visual unroll of what's happening in our reduce, so
看起来很不错。
it looks pretty good.
遗漏的一件事是我们没有最终的完整声明。
One thing that's missing is we don't have our complete statement on the end.
我们降价的最终结果是什么？
What is the end result of our reduction?
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：单个值。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: A single value.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：一个值，但它是什么？
&gt;&gt; Kyle: A single value but what is it?
&GT；&GT；Kyle：这是我们的承诺链。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: It's our promise chain.
我们能做些什么？
What can we do?
只是简单地提出另一个。然后在我们的承诺的结尾，并且
Just simply put another .then on the end of our Promise, and
输出完成消息。
output to complete message.
凯尔：什么事？
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Yes?
&gt；&gt；演讲者2：我们两个事件的顺序，返回承诺和
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: The order for our two events, the returning the Promise and
做输出。
doing the output.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：嗯哼。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Uh-huh.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：可能是相反的顺序，就像它不是我们以前的一样
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Could be in the opposite order like it wasn't our previous
锻炼？
exercise?
&gt；&gt；Kyle：不。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: No.
因为如果我们按照之前的顺序做，这就是它会做的事情。
Because if we did it in the previous order, here's what that would do.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：你发现问题了吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Do you spot the problem?
我们在这里放什么？
What are we out putting here?
我们最初承诺的空值。
An empty value from our initial Promise.
我们在这里输出的是什么？
What are we outputting here?
P1.
p1.
我们在这里放什么？
What are we out putting here?
P2。
p2.
谁在输出p3？
Who's outputting p3?
订购是绝对必要的。
The ordering is absolutely necessary.
凯尔：好的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: All right.
这是一个我们可以编写的实用程序。
That's a utility that we could write.
您不会想一遍又一遍地编写代码，您的地图和
You wouldn't want to write that code over and over again, your maps and
你的缺点。
your reduces.
但这是一个实用程序，我们可以将其封装到一个实用程序中，然后传递给它一个数组
But it's a utility we could wrap that up into a utility where we pass it an array
我们告诉它将所有这些响应排序在一起
of values and we tell it to sequence all these responses together and
然后我们可以在整个程序中重用该实用程序。
then we could reuse that utility all throughout our program.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：能够理解我们的小帮手朋友的价值
&gt;&gt; Kyle: The value of being able to understand our little helper friends like
映射和减少并发展一种问题的本能，例如，
map and reduce and developing an instinct for asking questions like,
等等，我基本上是在重复做某件事，
wait I'm fundamentally doing something repetitively,
为什么不直接将其放入列表上下文中，让工具为我重复它呢？
why not just put that into a list context and let the tools repeat it for me?
有时这是一个for循环，但是
Sometimes that's a for loop, but
有时，更高阶的模式(如map reduce)将帮助我们解决问题。
sometimes an even higher order pattern like a map reduce will help us out.
&GT；&GT；Kyle：关于练习四有什么问题吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Any questions about exercise four?
&gt；&gt；演讲者3：他们问的一件事是你是否履行了所有的承诺。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: One thing they're asking if you go down to all the Promise.
你会给所有这些匿名函数起什么名字？
What would you name all of those anonymous functions?
&gt；&gt；Kyle：[笑]是的，在我们这个愚蠢的例子中，
&gt;&gt; Kyle: [LAUGH] Yeah well in our silly example here,
我们真的没有太多的上下文来给我们好的命名。
we don't really have a lot of context to give us good naming for things.
如果我要命名这个匿名函数，我会说，chainP1，chainP2，
If I were gonna name this anonymous function I would say, chainP1, chainP2,
链接P3，因为我将确切地描述该函数不再做什么或
chainP3 because I would be describing exactly what that function does no more or
更少，它所做的是将P2，P1，P2和P3链成链。
less, and what it does is to chainP2, P1, P2 and P3 into the chain.
在这里，如果我想
Up here, if I wanted
要命名该匿名函数，我只需将其命名为chain p，chainPr。
to name that anonymous function I just call it chain p, chainPr.
我的本能是总是试图找到一些关于这东西正在做的事情的描述，
My instinct is to always try to find some description for what the thing is doing,
即使这是一个非常通用的描述，这仍然比匿名这个词好。
even if it's a very generic description, that still better than the word anonymous.
&GT；&GT；Kyle：关于这个练习还有其他问题吗？
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Any other questions about the exercise?
是啊。
Yes.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：我们是获得更高的性能[INAUDIBLE]还是
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Do we get more performance [INAUDIBLE] or
执行此映射然后降低或的任何性能
any performance doing this map and then reduce of or
取而代之的是我们在前面的练习中做的那个，我们和
instead having the one we did in the previous exercises where we and
为了给你，你的诺言分开[INAUDIBLE]。
to give the, you the Promises separate [INAUDIBLE].
&GT；&GT；Kyle：所以问题是，是否真的有性能差异。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: And so the question is, is there a performance difference not really.
没有真正的性能差异，这是这里的主要内容
There's no real performance difference this is the primary thing here is
功能。
functionality.
这是一种机制
This is a mechanism by which
我们可以有一个任意长的URL列表来编织在一起。
we can have an arbitrarily long list of URLs to weave together.
而在前面的示例中，它固定为3。
Whereas in the previous example, it's fixed at three.
因为我们的写作方式。
Because of the way that we wrote it.
它更多的是功能而不是性能。
It's more functionality than performance.
&gt；&gt；Kyle：是的，就像一般的提醒一样，如果你有什么问题
&gt;&gt; Kyle: Yeah, just as a general reminder, if you're having problems with something
我已经打了，这是完全可能的，有时我搞砸了
that I've typed, it is entirely possible that sometimes I flub up and
我想念打字什么的。
I miss type something or whatever.
但是练习档案
But the exercise files,
练习解决方案文件已经过定期测试，它们应该可以工作。
the exercise solution files have been regularly tested they should work.
对照练习文件中的内容检查自己。
Check yourself against what you've got in the exercise file.
那通常是一个很好的地方去找出哪里有，
That's usually a good place to try to ferret out where there's,
可能会有问题。
there might be an issue.